A Finding Aid to the Holger Cahill Papers, 1910-1993, bulk 1910-1960, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Writings, Lectures and Speeches, 1916-1960; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 1 Linear foot Boxes 14-15, 18
  4.5: Typescripts for Art For The Millions, 1936-1940
  - Lectures and Speeches by Cahill, 1930-1945; 4.1; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains typescripts of lectures and speeches by Cahill, many with hand-written notes and copies of drafts. Parts of some typescripts are missing. Material is arranged chronologically with undated material placed first.
    - [ Ernest Peixotto], undated; Archival Resource Key; (lecture notes) (Reel 5290, Frame 1020-1022)
    - WPA Lecture, Chicago, undated; Archival Resource Key; (lecture notes) (Reel 5290, Frame 1023-1025)
    - [ American Folk Art], Phillips Memorial Gallery, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1026-1066)
    - [ History of Support of American Art], undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1067-1085)
    - [ Government Support of Art], Radio Talk, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1086-1094)
    - Independents, Society of Independent Artists, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1095-1110)
    - [ Development of Visual Training Aids], U.S. Navy Training Aids Development Center, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1111-1124)
    - [ Crafts as Art], New Hampshire Talk, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1125-1144)
    - American Folk Art, Radio Talk, [November 1930]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1145-1154)
    - American Folk Sculpture, Newark Museum, 1931; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1155-1168)
    - New Horizons, Chicago, [1936]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1169-1197)
    - [ Women's Role in Art], Women's Democratic Club, May 24, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1198-1209)
    - Speech for Southern Women's National Democratic Organization, New York, December 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0319-0329)
    - [ Old and New Paths in American Design], Newark Museum, November 6, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1210-1250)
    - Art for the Few or the Many?, American Association of University Women, November 15, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1252-1271)
    - Untitled, FAP, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0330-0332)
    - [ Index of American Design], St. Louis, Missouri, January 31, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1272-1286)
    - [ WPA-FAP], Metropolitan Museum of Art, March 28, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1287-1332)
    - [ Aims and Achievements of the WPA-FAP], American Artists Congress, December 18, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1333-1355)
    - Child Art, April [1938]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1356-1362)
    - Goodyear Dinner speech, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1363-1371)
    - New Jersey Art at the World's Fair, Newark Museum Radio Talk, February 11, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1372-1378)
    - Dedication of Murals for WNYC Radio Studios, August 2, 1939; Archival Resource Key; (lecture notes) (Reel 5290, Frame 1379-1381)
    - Untitled, FAP, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 1105, Frame 0293-0302)
    - Untitled, FAP, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 1105, Frame 0305-0318)
    - Project Control Talk, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0303-0304)
    - What Is Tradition?, Artists' Congress, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1382-1402)
    - North Carolina Speech, April 1, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1403-1441)
    - Untitled, FAP, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 1105, Frame 0333-0346)
    - [ Contemporary American Art and Its Antecedents], Cosmopolitan Club, [1941]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1442-1489)
    - [ Support for Artists vs. Museums], American Federation of Arts, [1941]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1490-1493)
    - [ American Art History], American Institute of Decorators, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1494-1541)
    - Art in the National Defense, Radio Talk, January 27, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1542-1545)
    - The Face of America, Cosmopolitan Club, February 10, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5290, Frame 1546-1549)
    - The Face of America, Cosmopolitan Club, cont., February 10, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0005-0041)
    - [ Role of Art in the Community], People's Art Center Association, May 5, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0042-0078)
    - Art in Wartime, December 3, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0079-0081)
    - [ Use of Art in War], Dartmouth College, January 15, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0082-0098)
    - [ American Attraction to Art of the Far East], 1944; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0099-0106)
    - [ U. S. Government Art Projects, 1945]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0107-0130)
  - Lectures and Speeches by Others, 1916-1940; 4.2; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains typescripts of lectures and speeches by others, often with notes and copies of drafts. The majority of the material relates to the WPA FAP. Records are arranged chronologically with undated material placed first.
    - Pigmentation or Chemistry of Artists' Colors by K. R. Leipold, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0133-0140)
    - History of Painting by Henry H. McLellan, Jr., undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0141-0147)
    - [ Launching of California Supervisors] by Thomas C. Parker, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0148-0157)
    - An Edinburgh Address on Design and Industry by Frank Pick, October 1916; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0158-0174)
    - Museum Service to the Art Industries by Richard F. Bach, Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1927; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0175-0186)
    - Exhibition of American Folk Art at the Albright Art Gallery, Radio Talk by Nora Christensen, June 20, 1932; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0187-0198)
    - Public Works of Art Project by Edward Bruce, Advisory Committee to the Treasury on Fine Arts, January 17, 1934; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0199-0204)
    - The New Day in Negro Art by Harry H. Sutton, Jr., Bethune-Cookman College, Daytona Beach, Florida, January 17, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0205-0207)
    - The Negro in the Field of Painting and Sculpture by Harry H. Sutton, Jr., January 28, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0208-0212)
    - Mellon's Art by Maury Maverick, U. S. House of Representatives, March 1, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0213-0217)
    - Community Art Centers by Thomas C. Parker, May 4, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0218-0227)
    - [ Federal Art Project] by Thomas C. Parker, May 22, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0228-0257)
    - Opportunities for the Negro in American Art by Harry H. Sutton, Jr., Davis Street School, Jacksonville, November 2, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0258-0260)
    - The Highlights in Negro Art by Harry H. Sutton, Jr., Davis Street School, Jacksonville, February 9, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0261-0265)
    - The Opportunities of the Negro in Art by Harry H. Sutton, Jr., Davis Street School, Jacksonville, February 14, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0266-0269)
    - Federal Sponsored Community Art Centers by Thomas C. Parker, American Library Association, June 14, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0270-0291)
    - What Is the American Way? by Harry L. Hopkins, July 16, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0292-0306)
    - [ Negro Art] by Thomas C. Parker, Tuskegee Institute, July 29, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0307-0320)
    - Extension Remarks on Addresses in Honor of American Artists Who Have Decorated Federal Buildings by Elbert D. Thomas, U. S. Senate, April 25, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0321-0327)
    - Speech Before the Second National Conference on Handicrafts, Penland, North Carolina by Whitney Atchley, September 3, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0328-0336)
  - Writings by Cahill, 1928-1960; 4.3; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains typescripts of writings by Cahill, including book and exhibition reviews. A substantial portion of the material found here was written during Cahill's directorship of the FAP. Material is arranged chronologically with undated material placed first.
    - American Resources in the Arts, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0340-0395)
    - The Government in Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0396-0400)
    - Request for Opinions of FAP Program, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0401-0404)
    - Index of American Design: What It Is, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0405-0409)
    - [ Index of American Design], undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0410-0429)
    - The Stations of the Cross of San Gabriel Mission, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0430-0436)
    - [ Americans' Interest in Art], undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0437-0450)
    - [ Orientation Toward Living American Art], undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0451-0463)
    - Art in Democracy, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0464-0470)
    - Russia and the United States, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0471-0477)
    - The Icelandic Discovery of America, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0478-0485)
    - History of American Art Proposal, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0486-0491)
    - Concepts of Folk Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0492-0496)
    - American Folk Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0497-0505)
    - Folk Art, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0506-0682)
    - Puritan Imagination, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0683-0697)
    - [ Development of Modern American Art], undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0698-0702)
    - Description of American Art in a Portfolio, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0703-0719)
    - Industrial Design and Education, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0720-0725)
    - The New Literacy, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0726-0734)
    - Prefatory Note, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0735-0736)
    - Community Art Centers in the Western States, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0737-0741)
    - From Furniture to Politics, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0742-0744)
    - Exhibit of Steigel Glass at the National Museum, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0745-0749)
    - Review of Library of Congress Exhibition, [ Creative Art of the American Negro], undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1107-1113)
    - Exhibition Review, Ancient Arts of the Andes, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1114-1123)
    - Article Review, on Photography for Art in America by Kirstein, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1124-1128)
    - Book Review, Divided We Fought: A Pictorial History of the Civil War, 1861-1865 by David Donald, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1129-1133)
    - Book Review, The Meeting of the East and West by F.S.C. Northrop, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1134-1146)
    - Book Review, The Son of the Gamblin' Man by Mari Sandoz, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1147-1157)
    - Book Review, [ The Place of the Picture as Historical Document] by Mr. Taft, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1158-1164)
    - Industrial Art, 1928; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0750-0765)
    - [ William Zorach, 1932]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0766-0795)
    - Art of the Common Man, [1933]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0796-0813)
    - Art For Whom? A Survey of Present-Day Conditions in the Arts, [1935]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0814-0820)
    - [ Federal Art Project, 1936]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0821-0823)
    - The Federal Art Project, [1937]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0824-0838)
    - The Art Program, [1937]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0839-0841)
    - [ WPA Arts Program, 1937]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0842-0852)
    - Federal Art Project, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0853-0858)
    - Honors Won by WPA Artists, 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0859-0880)
    - [ Views on Modern Art in Time of War, 1942]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0881-0885)
    - Note on the Employment of Artists in War Time, [1942]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0886-0888)
    - [ Publication of the Index of American Design, 1942]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0889-0893)
    - [ Work of the WPA, 1944]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0894-0896)
    - [ Art As an Ingredient of National Unity], 1944; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0897-0916)
    - President Roosevelt and the U.S. Government Art Projects, [1945]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0917-0944)
    - After Forty Years, American Federation of Arts, [1949]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0945-0964)
    - Folk Art and the American Style (for House Beautiful), 1950; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0965-0993)
    - Homage to Morgan Russell, [1953]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 0994-1009)
    - Paris Catalog, 1955; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1010-1056)
    - Article for Marg Magazine on American Art in This Century, 1956; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1057-1105)
    - Book Review, George Caleb Bingham: River Portraitist by John Francis McDermott, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1165-1168)
    - Book Review, But Not for Love by Maynatalie Tabak, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1169-1171)
    - Miscellaneous Fragments of Typescripts, 1938-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1172-1223)
  - Writings by Others, 1932-1957; 4.4; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains typsecripts of writings by others, many of which were produced as part of the WPA FAP. Material is arranged chronologically with undated material placed first.
    - Artists Union by Unidentified Author, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1227-1229)
    - Dr. Samuel Butler by Unidentified Author, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1230-1231)
    - To Paint and Stain Glass and Porcelain by Unidentified Author, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1232-1234)
    - Memorandum on a Post-War Reorganization of the Section of Fine Arts and Other Federal Projects by George Biddle, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1235-1244)
    - Early Cowboy Art by E. J. Bird, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1245-1248)
    - American Artists' Congress by Stuart Davis, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1261-1264)
    - Jose Delores Lopez [by Meredith Hare], undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1265-1271)
    - An Architect's Point of View by William Lescaze, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1272-1274)
    - Art Comes to the People by Eugene Ludins, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1275-1284)
    - The Artists' Union by Stevens Maxey, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1285-1287)
    - America As Americans See It by Henry McBride, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1288-1289)
    - The Development of American Mural Painting by Geoffrey Norman, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1290-1298)
    - Easel Painting by Harley Perkins, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1299-1301)
    - Art and Social Therapy by Frances Pollak, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1302-1306)
    - A New Attitude on Art by Walter Quirt, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1307-1310)
    - Some American Primitives by Elsa Rogo, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1311-1320)
    - An Introduction to the Living World of Art by Lincoln Rothschild, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1321-1323)
    - The Revival of Mosaic by Arthur W. Sears, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1324-1330)
    - The Third Dimension Progresses: The Diorama Project by George T. Senseney, undated; Archival Resource Key; (includes photo of Senseney) (Reel 5291, Frame 1331-1342)
    - The Art of the Poster by George Melville Smith, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1343-1345)
    - Description of Sommer's Working Methods by William Sommer, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1346-1348)
    - Pottery Methods by Walter Speck, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1349-1354)
    - [ Widening of the Sculptor's Field] by Emmanuel Viviano, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1355-1359)
    - Poems by Max Weber, undated; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1360-1365)
    - Editors' Information from [ America As America Sees It] by Henry McBride, 1932; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1391-1394)
    - Zoar by Nixon of the Society of Separatists of Zoar, 1933; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1366-1383)
    - Simonson Article by [John Cotton Dana, 1935]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1384-1390)
    - Ancient and Renaissant Rome by Morgan Russell, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1395-1404)
    - Artists' Coordination Committee by Frederic Knight, [1936]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1405-1412)
    - Index of American Design by Ruth Reeves, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1413-1416)
    - Art and the State v. America by Lewis Mumford, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1417-1425)
    - [ Art Classes for Young People] by Samuel Friedman, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1426-1430)
    - [ Sunday Night Forums] by Dorothy Paris, [1936]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1431-1440)
    - Derivation and History of Weathervanes by Richard Farmer Smith, [1937]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1441-1443)
    - Tobacconists Figures, Research Notes Compiled by WPA Program, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1444-1475)
    - WPA Art Project Murals by Sheldon Cheney, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1249-1257)
    - A Long Term Program for the National Handicraft Association, Based on Reports Collected During the Summer of 1938 by Humphrey J. Emery, Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1476-1486)
    - The WPA Federal Art Project, Its Contribution to the American People by Fanny Bowles Vanderkooi, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1487-1492)
    - Urban Recreational Planning by Caroline C. Williams, [1941]; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1493-1515)
    - Those Who Support the Art Center by H. A. Zurbrick, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0004-0006)
    - [ John Cotton Dana] by M.D.C. Crawford, circa 1944; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5291, Frame 1258-1260)
    - [Review of Cahill's Book Look South to the Polar Star] by Unidentified Author, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0007-0010)
    - An American Renaissance and "The Pauper's Oath" by Helen C. Farrell, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0011-0078)
  - Typescripts For Art For The Millions, 1936-1940; 4.5; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries comprises typescripts by forty-eight of Cahill's colleagues discussing various media and philosphies of the visual arts used for the book Art For The Millions: Essays from the 1930s by Artists and Administrators of the WPA Federal Art Project, edited by Francis V. O'Connor (Boston: New York Graphic Society, 1973). Typescripts are arranged alphabetically by author.
    - Table of Contents (see also sol Box 18), circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0082-0093)
    - Abbott, Berenice, Changing New York, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0094-0097)
    - Brown, Douglas, Subject Matter in Painting, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0098-0100)
    - Brown, Samuel J., About Myself, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0101-0103)
    - Cashwan, Samuel, The Sculptor's Point of View, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0104-0107)
    - Clements, Grace, Organizing the Subconscious, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0108-0114)
    - Curtis, Philip C., The Phoenix Art Center, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0115-0119)
    - Davis, Stuart, The Social Education of the Artist, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0120-0125)
    - Davis, Stuart, Abstract Painting Today, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0127-0135)
    - Eichenberg, Fritz, Eulogy on the Woodblock, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0136-0139)
    - Gellert, Hugo, Artists Coordination Committee, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0141-0146)
    - Glassgold, C. Adolph, Recording American Design, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0147-0153)
    - Gorky, Arshile, My Murals for the Newark Airport: An Interpretation, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0154-0158)
    - Guglielmi, Louis, After the Locusts, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0159-0162)
    - Hayes, Vertis, The Negro Artist Today, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0163-0167)
    - Hayes, Vertis, The Position of Art in Present Day Society As I See It, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0168-0173)
    - Hiler, Hilaire, An Approach to Mural Decoration, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0174-0177)
    - Hunter, R. Vernon, An Interpretation of Patrocino Barela, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0178-0181)
    - Kopman, Benjamin, Notes on Art, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0182-0185)
    - La More, Chet, The Artists Union of America, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0186-0188)
    - Lemmon, Warren W., Native Arts of the Southwest, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0189-0208)
    - Levine, Jack, Street Scene, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key; (1 of 2) (Reel 5292, Frame 0209-0210)
    - Levine, Jack, Street Scene, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key; (2 of 2) (Reel 5292, Frame 212)
    - Macdonald-Wright, Stanton, Sculpture in Southern California, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0213-0219)
    - McMahon, Audrey, The Federal Art Project and the Artist, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0220-0223)
    - Moylan, Lloyd, Mural Opportunities, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0224-0226)
    - Murray, Hester Miller, Concerning Subject Matter, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0227-0229)
    - Newell, James Michael, The Use of Symbols in Mural Painting, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0230-0237)
    - Norman, Geoffrey, The Development of American Mural Painting, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0238-0244)
    - Olds, Elizabeth, Prints for Mass Production, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0245-0252)
    - Palo-Kangas, John, Thought-Forms in Red Sandstone, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0253-0255)
    - Park, Paul, Photography As An Art, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Reel 5292, Frame 0256-0259)